drug-education-resource.com 2012-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Drug Education Resource

Privacy Statement of Drug Education Resource

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The privacy, confidence, and trust of individuals who visit our website is important to us. No personal information is collected at this site unless provided voluntarily by an individual while participating in an activity that asks for the information.

**Cookies** "Cookies" are small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. Cookies do not damage your system. They are used to keep track of and store information so the user does not have to supply the information multiple times. The information that is collected through cookies at this site is handled in the same manner as other information collected here. You can configure your web browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when a web site attempts to send you a cookie. You can also check your hard drive for cookie files and delete them from your computer.

**Links to Other Sites** This website contains links to many other websites. These include links to websites operated by other government agencies, nonprofit organizations, and private businesses. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites and suggest you review their privacy statements.

**NOTIFICATION and CHANGES** Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected here. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes. 

Permissions to Link or Post Permission is granted for linking to our site, individual pages or articles within the site. **  
Copyright (c) 2009 Drug Education Resource. All rights reserved.**

[San Jose drug rehab](http://www.camprecovery.com/) We not only teach individuals a way to keep faraway from drug, however a way to live happy and successful lives so there's not any want to use drugs.

[Bulimia Treatment](http://www.casapalmera.com/treatments/bulimia-treatment.php) Our treatment program emphasizes the need for individuals to cope with the complex emotions that cause them to doubt this right and highlights the need for the individual to take themselves and their physical and psychological needs seriously.

[www.drjaw.net](http://www.drjaw.net/treatment/braces/) Using tooth colored brackets and a new cutting edge white wire we can straighten your teeth in an average time of 6 months.

[Tummy Tuck Seattle](http://www.drsalemy.com/tummy_tuck.html) Tummy tuck Seattle gives patients a flatter stomach and is performed by experienced surgeons at Dr. Salemy's Cosmetic Surgery.

[Meals delivered](http://diettogo.com/) Don't have Time to Cook? Try Diet-to-Go Meal Delivery and lose weight FAST!

[Dental Tucson](http://www.johnrcarsondds.com/) Tucson Dentistry is your number one source for Tucson dentist, Tucson dentists, Tucson cosmetic dentist, gentle dentistry Tucson and more.

[cary family practice](http://www.trianglephysicianspc.com/cary-family-practice-doctor-healthcare/) The CARY FAMILY HEALTHCARE, NC office specializes in the Family Medicine discipline.Call 919-467-7528 or schedule an appointment with our online application today.

[Mexican Online Pharmacy](http://www.medicinesmexico.com/faqs.htm) We're number one online pharmacies.Order weight loss, anxiety, pain, depression treatment without prescription.Free shipping offer and express shipping available.

[www.candidayeastsupport.com](http://www.candidayeastsupport.com/ "www.candidayeastsupport.com") \- Finally! Fast Help For Those Suffering From Candida Yeast! Do you suffer from any of these issues - Digestive Problems, Things like gas, bloating or acid reflux.contact us today!

[MEDICAL STAFFING](http://medical-staffing.net/) Apply now with Medical Staffing Resources and let our team of experienced recruiters guide you through the maze of the application process

[Rehab in California](http://www.drugrehabranch.com/) Best California drug rehab. Call NOW for a FREE drug or alcohol rehab assessment! we tend to are one in all the foremost exclusive and opulent rehab centers in California.

[Crest Whitening Strips](http://www.teethwhiteningkits2you.co.uk/Crest-Whitening-Strips/c6/index.html) Buy Crest white teeth whitening strips with Free UK delivery low prices at TeethWhiteningKits2You Tooth whitening made simple at home with Crest whitestrips.

[Advanced Affordable diabetic supplies](http://www.advancedaffordablediabetics.com/) Diabetic supplies for uninsured including glucose meters, glucose test strips & blood sugar monitors at affordable prices. Get diabetes supplies right to your home! Call us at 1-877-441-5151!

[San Jose drug rehab](http://www.camprecovery.com/) We not only teach individuals a way to keep faraway from drug, however a way to live happy and successful lives so there's not any want to use drugs.

[Bulimia Treatment](http://www.casapalmera.com/treatments/bulimia-treatment.php) Our treatment program emphasizes the need for individuals to cope with the complex emotions that cause them to doubt this right and highlights the need for the individual to take themselves and their physical and psychological needs seriously.

[www.drjaw.net](http://www.drjaw.net/treatment/braces/) Using tooth colored brackets and a new cutting edge white wire we can straighten your teeth in an average time of 6 months.

[MEDICAL STAFFING](http://medical-staffing.net/) Apply now with Medical Staffing Resources and let our team of experienced recruiters guide you through the maze of the application process

[Arizona treatment centers](http://www.treatment-centers.net/directory/arizona.html) If you’re looking for a professional treatment center in Arizona, we suggest www.treatment-centers.net. You can read reviews and view ratings to help you choose the best center for you or your loved one. Find the help you need today!

[Best protein powders](http://www.nutritiondiscounters.com/protein_powders_s/1.htm) Nutrition Discounters store in the US offering a full range of high quality sports nutrition and protein supplements, also includes high quality whey protein, sports supplements and bodybuilding supplements which are all manufactured and delivered by us.
